<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Turism</string>
    <string name="paqueteTuristico"> Enter person number</string>
    <string name="calcular">Calculate package </string>
    <string name="descripcion1"> hiking: a journey on foot to harmonize with the land through lush
        natural landscapes with beautiful panoramas, crystal clear streams and the very physical demand
        of an adventurous spirit.</string>
    <string name="descripcion2">Christ the King: When you arrive at Támesis, one of the first things that will draw
        your attention will surely be the hill Christ the King because the mountain and its statue "reign" over the people.
        The hill is a symbol of this typical village of the southwest of Antioquia and also offers a beautiful view over the
        entire Cártama Valley, the Farallón de la Pintada and even the Cauca River. The walk lasts about 3 hours, it is not
        long but it is demanding because a part of the path is quite inclined and passes through a tropical humid fog forest,
        where when it is good sun this same road becomes a strong ascent. Its summit rewards those who conquer it by a panoramic
        view of its almost 360°..</string>
    <string name="descripcion3"> Torrentism: Torrentism activity in Tamesis takes place in the waterfall of La Peinada,
        which is accessed through a route along the pre-Hispanic road, built centuries ago by the Cartama culture. The
        descent of 70 m in rappel is an exciting and fun adventure in which you will experience new sensations.. </string>
    <string name="actividad1">Trekking</string>
    <string name="edad1">Age 12-70</string>
    <string name="horario1">schedule 8-3</string>
    <string name="actividad2">Christ the King</string>
    <string name="edad2">Edad 12-65</string>
    <string name="horario2">horario 8-3</string>
    <string name="actividad3">Torrentism</string>
    <string name="edad3">Edad 15-50</string>
    <string name="horario3">horario 8-12</string>

    <string name="opcion1">About us</string>
    <string name="opcion2">English</string>
    <string name="opcion3">Espanish</string>


    <string name="perfilNombre">Alicia Ardila Aguirre</string>

    <string name="perfil">My name is Alicia Ardila, I am a systems engineer at the ITM Metropolitan Institute of Technology.
        Currently working at ElicoGroup Automation Engineering and Industrial Information Systems company, in there I Managing
        Social Networks and the content of the website and, I also provide support in the commercial area..</string>

    <string name="vermas">See+</string>

</resources>